{"text": "Taking care of our people is my number one priority.\"", "metadata": {"source": "Kronos Star", "filename": "630.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8051601052284241}
{"text": "LOCATION: ELODIS, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "182.txt", "date": "2007/03/21", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 16, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8966478705406189}
{"text": "Pondo Reese, writer of the weekly newspaper of Elodis, is held with its window, looking at outside towards the sun placing on the river of Tiskele.", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "622.txt", "date": "1998/05/17", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 11, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 47, "end": 53, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 139, "end": 146, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9139705300331116}
{"text": "Requests for information were met with assurances that the police,  whose custody Karel was in at the time of his death, would do everything possible to perform an exhaustive investigation.", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "77.txt", "date": "2011/06/21", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 82, "end": 87, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8783490657806396}
{"text": "SOURCE: International Times\nTITLE: Kronos' oil and gas industry has warned it faces its \"biggest challenge in 20 years\" due to the low levels of exploration.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "238.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 27, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 35, "end": 41, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7257289886474609}
{"text": "GAStech has estimated that the Kronos total offshore shale gas resources could be between five and 10 times the size of the resources available onshore.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "751.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 15}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 7, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 31, "end": 37, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8669627904891968}
{"text": "For roughly 6 hours GAStech - Kronos employee Edvard Vann was interrogated by Kronos Police and Government officials before being released at 17:00 this evening.", "metadata": {"source": "The Abila Post", "filename": "50.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 20, "end": 27, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 30, "end": 36, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 46, "end": 57, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 78, "end": 91, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9579459428787231}
{"text": "Bianca said that it never has seen east level of the activity related to the overdoses of the drug in the seven years that it has handled the department of the emergency and in the 20 years she has been nurse.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "93.txt", "date": "2013/02/09", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 6, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8203554749488831}
{"text": "The conservative government Kronos used an emergency situation law to threaten unless protestors with arrest they spread and on the work returned.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "318.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 28, "end": 34, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7981696128845215}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 1994/09/24\n \nLOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "News Online Today", "filename": "534.txt", "date": "1994/09/24", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 34, "end": 39, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 41, "end": 47, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9057978987693787}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2007/03/22", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "236.txt", "date": "2007/03/22", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9223037362098694}
{"text": "\"Sten has always been a champion for the children of Tethys,\" said Hospital President Willem Gracias.", "metadata": {"source": "The World", "filename": "750.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 1, "end": 5, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 53, "end": 59, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 67, "end": 75, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 86, "end": 100, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8211933374404907}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 1999/11/15", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "701.txt", "date": "1999/11/15", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9227825999259949}
{"text": "2014/01/20", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "525.txt", "date": "2009/02/21", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.890731692314148}
{"text": "TITLE: Profile:  Elian Karel", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "149.txt", "date": "2009/06/23", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 17, "end": 28, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9544534087181091}
{"text": "\"We've made a good living for a long time,\" Reese tells me.", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "154.txt", "date": "2012/09/08", "sentence_index": 19}, "spans": [{"start": 44, "end": 49, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9313549399375916}
{"text": "The demonstrators in Abilia, Kronos put fire at the buildings of government, in another round of faintness in this torn city", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "126.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 21, "end": 27, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 29, "end": 35, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.883013129234314}
{"text": "The hypocrisy of bringing in foreigners our to tell that open of our country for foreigners for our bad is ludicrous and is clearly a sign of mental sickness is in they which resists himself our modernization.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "406.txt", "date": "1998/01/19", "sentence_index": 14}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8706845045089722}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The General Post", "filename": "835.txt", "date": "1992/12/13", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "We intend improve the measure and the minister Nespola  later on the year introduce it again.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "187.txt", "date": "2001/03/24", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 47, "end": 54, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7384821772575378}
{"text": "Edvard Vann, GAStech - the guard of safety of Kronos which was questioned and released after 6 a.m., indicated the guards of Kronos were suspectés as being the criminals behind events of today.", "metadata": {"source": "The Light of Truth", "filename": "494.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 11, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 13, "end": 20, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 46, "end": 52, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 125, "end": 131, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.6993078589439392}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "374.txt", "date": "2013/06/20", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "I asked to him about its life in the farm.", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "317.txt", "date": "1998/03/21", "sentence_index": 32}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9296561479568481}
{"text": "1522 - It seems that to it employs of GAStech are permetted to leave the centers.", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "486.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 38, "end": 45, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.868789553642273}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Wrap", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "271.txt", "date": "2000/06/02", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 12, "end": 16, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8901165723800659}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 21 January 2014", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "624.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9164304137229919}
{"text": "The availability and the access of the material up to capital are the two important barriers which are noted by our ministry.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "457.txt", "date": "2012/02/21", "sentence_index": 15}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8433583378791809}
{"text": "SOURCE: Centrum Sentinel", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "485.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8743123412132263}
{"text": "GAStech has decided to contribute $200 million towards the cost of the harbor improvements in exchange for the preferential location of its terminal of the gas in the new port and has resigned to berth the honorary percents years.", "metadata": {"source": "The Guide", "filename": "725.txt", "date": "1993/09/21", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 7, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8998690247535706}
{"text": "One new aid group, GIVING Singapore have been recently been in reply to the conflict in Kosovo.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "302.txt", "date": "1999/11/16", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 19, "end": 35, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 88, "end": 94, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8974288702011108}
{"text": "The protectors of Kronos (POK) met in front of the district headquarterses of GAStech in Abila arrested to the dozens of demonstrators taking care of to violate this morning.", "metadata": {"source": "The Guide", "filename": "837.txt", "date": "2009/02/19", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 26, "end": 29, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 78, "end": 85, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 89, "end": 94, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8637614846229553}
{"text": "LOCATION: DAVOS, Switzerland", "metadata": {"source": "The Light of Truth", "filename": "432.txt", "date": "2010/12/18", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 28, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8703567385673523}
{"text": "The government of Kronos so continues offering either the test for the residents in a matter of Elodis or as plans to far investigate the more the causes by the root of the diseases in and around the municipality.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "703.txt", "date": "1997/10/16", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 96, "end": 102, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8549405932426453}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2014/01/20", "metadata": {"source": "News Online Today", "filename": "291.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9286735653877258}
{"text": "He costs what costs, Julian he felt well to martyr of the first POK and has used the image of Julian in the Literature of the campaign since.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "300.txt", "date": "2012/08/24", "sentence_index": 14}, "spans": [{"start": 21, "end": 27, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 64, "end": 67, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 94, "end": 100, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 108, "end": 125, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7250632047653198}
{"text": "In a show of corporate largesse GAStech International vows to donate money to the remaining family members.", "metadata": {"source": "The Abila Post", "filename": "756.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 32, "end": 53, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.719415009021759}
{"text": "Q: Are there situations in which to be a foreign director is really an advantage?", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "279.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 54}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8197042942047119}
{"text": "Nevertheless, I believe that it is important like minister of the health to run errand due and to investigate the information of the disease near the municipality of Elodis.", "metadata": {"source": "The Guide", "filename": "330.txt", "date": "1998/11/10", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 166, "end": 172, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7960624098777771}
{"text": "Fields \"of Kronos indicated by Jecovic contain an abundance of oil and the gas to be still found and it is critical find us the means of turning the current state of exploration around.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "739.txt", "date": "2012/02/21", "sentence_index": 14}, "spans": [{"start": 11, "end": 17, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 31, "end": 38, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.866809070110321}
{"text": "The groundbreaking today at the Tiskele Bend site marks another flag planted in foreign soil by GAStech International.", "metadata": {"source": "The World", "filename": "84.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 32, "end": 44, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 96, "end": 117, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8813506364822388}
{"text": "However, with smashing WFA to attribute to the financing of questions, the requirements of POK were mainly ignored and downplayed.", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "709.txt", "date": "2012/08/23", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [{"start": 23, "end": 26, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 91, "end": 94, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.6989373564720154}
{"text": "I will not let the day be run off the line by nonfounded, libelous allegations.\"", "metadata": {"source": "The Light of Truth", "filename": "560.txt", "date": "2009/05/17", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7931089401245117}
{"text": "I usually up to the areas by sun, M. Henk Bodrogi tells me.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "183.txt", "date": "1998/04/26", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [{"start": 34, "end": 35, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 37, "end": 49, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9203552007675171}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Explainer", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "679.txt", "date": "2010/06/14", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8995077610015869}
{"text": "Continue reading the main story", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "238.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9027530550956726}
{"text": "In 1998, WFA carried out test on the water of Elodis finding the levels high of benzene, arsenic of toluene and xylene, barium, chromium, lead and selenium.", "metadata": {"source": "Athena Speaks", "filename": "74.txt", "date": "2012/08/24", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 9, "end": 12, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 46, "end": 52, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9013726115226746}
{"text": "TITLE: POK REPRESENTATIVES MEET WITH KRONOS MINISTER OF HEALTH", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "420.txt", "date": "1998/11/15", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 37, "end": 43, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 56, "end": 62, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8982348442077637}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "Kronos Star", "filename": "541.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2007/03/22", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "390.txt", "date": "2007/03/22", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9223037362098694}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2009/05/16", "metadata": {"source": "Who What News", "filename": "422.txt", "date": "2009/05/16", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9161073565483093}
{"text": "Its coordinator has answered a lot tersely that  Mr. Vasco-Pais is not available and has detached the call.", "metadata": {"source": "Tethys News", "filename": "510.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 53, "end": 58, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 59, "end": 63, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7156146168708801}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 1993/09/21", "metadata": {"source": "The General Post", "filename": "723.txt", "date": "1993/09/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9166200757026672}
{"text": "They have damaged to the dozens of people in the perceived corruption excessive of the government of the protests and the perceived incapacity of politicians to improve the situation.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "608.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8850840330123901}
{"text": "Jecovic stated \"Kronos' fields contain an abundance of oil and gas yet to be found and it is critical we find the means to turn the current state of exploration around.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "238.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 7, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 16, "end": 22, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8251209855079651}
{"text": "They go to seem to it stupid.", "metadata": {"source": "Athena Speaks", "filename": "64.txt", "date": "2011/07/29", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8580467104911804}
{"text": "1330 UPDATE - At 1315 we placed a call to GAStech headquarters.", "metadata": {"source": "The Abila Post", "filename": "450.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 42, "end": 49, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9567164778709412}
{"text": "In the course of the years we a couple has here and there added hectare.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "183.txt", "date": "1998/04/26", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8822396397590637}
{"text": "SOURCE: The General Post", "metadata": {"source": "The General Post", "filename": "835.txt", "date": "1992/12/13", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8971437215805054}
{"text": "But in certain negotiations or certain questions such as the goods of luxury, the foreign Presidents can be an advantage.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "279.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 57}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7864543199539185}
{"text": "Eventually, locals downriver were evacuated.", "metadata": {"source": "The World", "filename": "498.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 10}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8775383234024048}
{"text": "Exploration has proved a controversial issue in Kronos>>\nContinue reading the main story\t\nThe son of the founder of gas firm GAStech is planning a venture to drill in the Mediterranean Sea, the Times has learned.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "751.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 48, "end": 54, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 125, "end": 132, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 171, "end": 188, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 194, "end": 199, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8002322316169739}
{"text": "I asked him concerning its life on the agriculture company.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "183.txt", "date": "1998/04/26", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9294497966766357}
{"text": "The police force used teargas to divide the undisciplined mob.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "318.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 19}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8012315034866333}
{"text": "He hoped to be sent in the days next and the return to his work with the protectors of Kronos, and was excited to continue the protectors of the mission of Kronos to which he dedicated his life.", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "269.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 87, "end": 93, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 156, "end": 162, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9390904903411865}
{"text": "Several instances of rioting in and around Elodis have been reported including the trashing of government buildings, rock throwing, and tire burnings.", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "113.txt", "date": "2005/09/25", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 43, "end": 49, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7906691431999207}
{"text": "Of nine years - the old boy initially survived the discharge and flown to the hospital of children Abila, but had been explained on arrival.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "100.txt", "date": "2007/03/19", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 99, "end": 104, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8897494673728943}
{"text": "John Rathburn, an American expert on executive kidnappings who is living in Tethys, says that Kronos has not been known as an archetypal country for kidnapping.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "167.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 13, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 18, "end": 26, "label": "EVENT"}, {"start": 76, "end": 82, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 94, "end": 100, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8284571170806885}
{"text": "Authorities in Abila said \"cotton candy\" may have been a factor in the death of 54-year-old Ralf Potter, whose bruised and naked body was found February 4 along a dead-end road.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 15, "end": 20, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 92, "end": 103, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7134178280830383}
{"text": "They hanker to, she said.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "530.txt", "date": "2013/02/08", "sentence_index": 34}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8869091272354126}
{"text": "They quote president Dorel Kapelou II of Kronos then saying he would be summoning an urgent meeting of the superior direction to deal with the \"threat the terrorist\" in the country.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "608.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 22}, "spans": [{"start": 21, "end": 37, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 41, "end": 47, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7813148498535156}
{"text": "They wore uniforms and has license plates.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "680.txt", "date": "2001/09/02", "sentence_index": 20}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9128977060317993}
{"text": "I asked him concerning its life on the agriculture company.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "448.txt", "date": "1998/03/21", "sentence_index": 32}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9294497966766357}
{"text": "Update, 7:40 PM:  The Carman has informed the pressed one that the police does not believe that missing people had left the island of Kronos.", "metadata": {"source": "Tethys News", "filename": "600.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 22, "end": 28, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 134, "end": 140, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7795434594154358}
{"text": "The competition under Kronosian and foreign firms is tough.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "535.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [{"start": 22, "end": 31, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7442643046379089}
{"text": "Its death, thought with being a murder by, encouraged much cancel gatherings to bring the message of the guards of Kronos to the public.", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "0.txt", "date": "2012/09/08", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [{"start": 115, "end": 121, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7835381627082825}
{"text": "Update, 11:45:  The civil employees of fire unit allow that the construction employs of GAStech king-enter.", "metadata": {"source": "Tethys News", "filename": "92.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 88, "end": 95, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9318773746490479}
{"text": "The tax incentives aim specifically the companies of the energy development, which tempt the government hopes to the realms of Kronos, but still undeveloped, gas fields.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "632.txt", "date": "1993/01/20", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 127, "end": 133, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7740213871002197}
{"text": "A unifying theme of the protesters was the chanted slogans including \"Justice for Elian\" in reference to previously mentioned activist Elian Karel and \"Remember Juliana\", a young girl from Elodis who died in 1998 allegedly from the effects of water contamination.", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "745.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 82, "end": 87, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 135, "end": 146, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 152, "end": 160, "label": "EVENT"}, {"start": 161, "end": 168, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 189, "end": 195, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7485833168029785}
{"text": "1840 - Homeland Illumination correspondent Petrus Gerhard reports that airport officials have released information that a private jet arrived at Abila airport earlier today, and that the jet was met by a waiting limousine.", "metadata": {"source": "Homeland Illumination", "filename": "804.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 7, "end": 28, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 43, "end": 57, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 145, "end": 150, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9529693722724915}
{"text": "This particular mixture of drug MDMC, also known by its street names the \"caramel of cotton\", the \"spice soña\" and the \"flower of tulip\", was found previously only in Asteria but it has made his way to the streets of Tethys and other international countries.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "234.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 32, "end": 36, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 167, "end": 174, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 217, "end": 223, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8819695115089417}
{"text": "But drilling at sea avoids the need for difficult negotiations with the councils, the communities and the holder of piece buildings.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "771.txt", "date": "1984/05/04", "sentence_index": 15}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7997583150863647}
{"text": "And it is that vision of healthy and we must honor thriving future for all here today.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "116.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 19}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8770029544830322}
{"text": "The empire GAStech has 2 thousand cows and 3 thousand pigs in its company agriculture companies, runs gyms, and offers to subsidized holiday in the resort of the black sea for very important employees.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "580.txt", "date": "2013/02/24", "sentence_index": 14}, "spans": [{"start": 11, "end": 18, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7102319598197937}
{"text": "The reception was loved to celebrate the company and our country the 20th year cooperation between.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "463.txt", "date": "2014/01/21", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.986689567565918}
{"text": "SOURCE: Central Bulletin", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "673.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8636624217033386}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "357.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "and interviewed the remaining employees GAStech.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "607.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 40, "end": 47, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9340314269065857}
{"text": "SOURCE: Centrum Sentinel", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "308.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8743123412132263}
{"text": "They are so militant in their false-directed belief which they manufactured claims that the foreign companies poison our children with their technology.", "metadata": {"source": "Worldwise", "filename": "196.txt", "date": "1998/01/19", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8945311307907104}
{"text": "The opened ports, people POK moved themselves and the freight carriages dissipated.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "680.txt", "date": "2001/09/02", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [{"start": 25, "end": 28, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8340402841567993}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "361.txt", "date": "2011/06/22", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "The declaration decides with Sanjorge, Jr. requires that set up the government of Kronos to insure my employees, but all citizens the not only security of of Kronos.", "metadata": {"source": "The Tulip", "filename": "529.txt", "date": "2009/02/22", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [{"start": 29, "end": 37, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 39, "end": 41, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 82, "end": 88, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 158, "end": 164, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8586946129798889}
{"text": "Know you why he takes a ladder with him to the hypermarket?", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "268.txt", "date": "2009/06/23", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9054211378097534}
{"text": "SOURCE: Central Bulletin", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "565.txt", "date": "2009/02/19", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 24, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8636624217033386}
{"text": "One of the pins could have blown out of the collar, releasing the gas, which then contacted a spark.", "metadata": {"source": "Athena Speaks", "filename": "295.txt", "date": "2000/08/18", "sentence_index": 10}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8727439641952515}
{"text": "Lawyer of Karel, Michale Kraft, released a declaration explanatory that the charges were against its customer false and that he hoped have Karel delivered of police force preservation at the end of the week.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "561.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 17, "end": 30, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 139, "end": 144, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7851406931877136}
{"text": "Police spokesman Adrien Carman said, \"We allowed the group some latitude with their rally, but when GAStech complained that the protestors were blocking entrance to their building, we had to take action.", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "565.txt", "date": "2009/02/19", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 17, "end": 30, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 100, "end": 107, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7619351148605347}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Wrap", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "408.txt", "date": "1998/11/15", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 12, "end": 16, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8901165723800659}
{"text": "The head of GAStech, Sten Sanjorge, Jr, that photo watches fixedly towards outside calendars and of marks throughout in the country, recognizes \"state inside the accusations of a state\", but she discusses that the necessities of the company simply to take care of his workers and of the communities around them.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "147.txt", "date": "2013/02/24", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [{"start": 12, "end": 19, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 21, "end": 38, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9151990413665771}
{"text": "President Kapelou II of the democratic party of Kronos caught 98.7% of the poll with Ren Touvi of the organization of matter and the party of the Union distant Second with pure 1.0% of the poll.", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "588.txt", "date": "2010/10/03", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 20, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 48, "end": 54, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 85, "end": 94, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 118, "end": 124, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 146, "end": 151, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 160, "end": 166, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9154399037361145}
{"text": "LOCATION: ELODIS, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "617.txt", "date": "1998/05/16", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 16, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8966478705406189}
{"text": "LOCATION: ELODIS, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "222.txt", "date": "1998/05/17", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 16, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8966478705406189}
{"text": "The jet instituted second as reported it has been directed towards Rome, Italy.", "metadata": {"source": "Modern Rubicon", "filename": "772.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 67, "end": 71, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 73, "end": 78, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9426968693733215}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "436.txt", "date": "2014/01/19", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "SOURCE: Kronos Star\nTITLE: Breaking: Emergency at GAStech Headquarters Building [Updates]\nAUTHOR: Cato Rossini, Marcella Trapani\nPUBLISHED: 20 January 2014", "metadata": {"source": "Kronos Star", "filename": "321.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 19, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 50, "end": 57, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 98, "end": 110, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 112, "end": 128, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8900871872901917}
{"text": "The police force says that they have a driver of 25 year old truck in the guard with the prison of Elodis.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "6.txt", "date": "2007/03/20", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 99, "end": 105, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8939982056617737}
{"text": "The report came in response to the gathering from the protest from one Wednesday by the POK with the registered offices from GAStech - from Kronos.", "metadata": {"source": "The Light of Truth", "filename": "675.txt", "date": "2009/02/21", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 88, "end": 91, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 125, "end": 132, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 140, "end": 146, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9481934905052185}
{"text": "The oldest and larger environmental organization of Kronos of activist", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "646.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [{"start": 52, "end": 58, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7819947004318237}
{"text": "Attacking a police force civil servant and destroying government possession is serious crime, Carmen said.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "480.txt", "date": "2013/12/16", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 94, "end": 100, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7524234056472778}
{"text": "Local GAStech executives Ingrid Barranco, Ada Campo-Corrente, Orhan Strum, and Willem Vasco-Pais will attend a reception with government officials tomorrow following a business meeting at their headquarters building.", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "436.txt", "date": "2014/01/19", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 6, "end": 13, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 25, "end": 40, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 42, "end": 51, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 52, "end": 60, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 62, "end": 73, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 79, "end": 91, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 92, "end": 96, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9240370392799377}
{"text": "A Protectors of Kronos demonstration was held in front of Abila police headquarters yesterday morning.", "metadata": {"source": "Kronos Star", "filename": "508.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 2, "end": 22, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 58, "end": 63, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9478119611740112}
{"text": "LOCATION: ELODIS, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "113.txt", "date": "2005/09/25", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 16, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 18, "end": 24, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8966478705406189}
{"text": "TITLE: Four people have died in a discharge near Elodis", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "100.txt", "date": "2007/03/19", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 49, "end": 55, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8126370310783386}
{"text": "SOURCE: News Online Today", "metadata": {"source": "News Online Today", "filename": "219.txt", "date": "2014/01/21", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 25, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8630812764167786}
{"text": "The criminals will then work the car with spray-painted emblems violate POK.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "480.txt", "date": "2013/12/16", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 72, "end": 75, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8155354857444763}
{"text": "One year suffered young people died today in search of a rosier future for its compatriots in cold, cement prison.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "158.txt", "date": "2010/06/21", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9030633568763733}
{"text": "LOCATION: CENTRUM, Tethys", "metadata": {"source": "The World", "filename": "195.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 17, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 19, "end": 25, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9034420847892761}
{"text": "With all the votes counted the democratic party of the president of Kronos now maintains 85 seats in the General Assembly, 13 for the organization of the business and the party of the unions, and 2 for the party of the industrialists of Kronos.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "382.txt", "date": "2010/10/04", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 68, "end": 74, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 105, "end": 121, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 237, "end": 243, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8243425488471985}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2014/01/21", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "396.txt", "date": "2014/01/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9236261248588562}
{"text": "There is still speculation concerning which in removal was taken and if President GAStech and CEO Sten Sanjorge Jr. ones the aim was, seen international GAStech has to a declaration to the press still take off.", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "818.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 82, "end": 89, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 98, "end": 114, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 153, "end": 160, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8850173950195312}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The Tulip", "filename": "479.txt", "date": "1992/12/12", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "TITLE: ANNIVERSARY OF PROTESTS", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "334.txt", "date": "2010/06/14", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.786661684513092}
{"text": "Marek asks all concerned citizens to join her to bring awareness to the problem of political corruption and favoritism pervasive in the offices of the government of Kronos.", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "135.txt", "date": "2012/04/09", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 5, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 165, "end": 171, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8073099851608276}
{"text": "The last thing which we have wanted to happen were for become to be hurt employee GAStech who by the mob only because he tried will work.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "165.txt", "date": "2009/02/19", "sentence_index": 10}, "spans": [{"start": 82, "end": 89, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7847137451171875}
{"text": "They say to us that there are been making the caramel of cotton or the synthetic marijuana.\"", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "93.txt", "date": "2013/02/09", "sentence_index": 15}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.840842068195343}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "474.txt", "date": "1995/10/12", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "\"They crave it,\" she said.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 33}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8057680130004883}
{"text": "SOURCE: World Source", "metadata": {"source": "World Source", "filename": "132.txt", "date": "2012/06/20", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 20, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7940601110458374}
{"text": "The IPO filings show that the executive group earned a collective $327.25 million from the newly vested shares including $96.25 million each for CFO Ingrid Barranco, CIO Ada Campo-Corrente, and COO Orhan Strum.", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "170.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 4, "end": 7, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 149, "end": 164, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 166, "end": 173, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 174, "end": 179, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 180, "end": 188, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 198, "end": 209, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7108721733093262}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2012/06/21", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "318.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9280537366867065}
{"text": "SOURCE: All News Today", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "135.txt", "date": "2012/04/09", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 22, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8560951948165894}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 1998/08/20", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "275.txt", "date": "1998/08/20", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9221917986869812}
{"text": "At this point, however, small girl was damaged too much to recover.", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "275.txt", "date": "1998/08/20", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8457217216491699}
{"text": "This agreement and port extension are the introduction of Kronos to the world!", "metadata": {"source": "The Tulip", "filename": "315.txt", "date": "1993/09/21", "sentence_index": 10}, "spans": [{"start": 58, "end": 64, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8728050589561462}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Tulip", "metadata": {"source": "The Tulip", "filename": "504.txt", "date": "2000/08/16", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 11, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 12, "end": 17, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8552829027175903}
{"text": "The spokesman Rufus Drymiau of government announced the movement, which will give to the authorities more power to split downwards on the POK.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "646.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 8}, "spans": [{"start": 14, "end": 27, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 138, "end": 141, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9062813520431519}
{"text": "A gathering of the hundreds of protestateurs combined with \"guards the movement of Kronos\" turned to violence today as the annoyed activists exhaled their dissatisfaction on the innocent citizens with Abila after having heard the news of died of Elian Karel of the Chief of POK.", "metadata": {"source": "Worldwise", "filename": "309.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 83, "end": 89, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 201, "end": 206, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 246, "end": 257, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 274, "end": 277, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8051788210868835}
{"text": "Rough 20 kilometers of by waters above are the site of the curve of Tiskele worked by GAStech International in governmental earth.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "731.txt", "date": "1997/04/25", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 68, "end": 75, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 86, "end": 107, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9166035652160645}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2010/03/05", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "242.txt", "date": "2010/03/05", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9256667494773865}
{"text": "Chanted the defenders behave signs POK with pictures of Karel and Juliana Vann, slogans, and strike candles to.", "metadata": {"source": "The Truth", "filename": "581.txt", "date": "2010/06/22", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 35, "end": 38, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 56, "end": 61, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 66, "end": 78, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8349440097808838}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "821.txt", "date": "1999/07/04", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "It is an European value that Kronosians is very responsivo a.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "656.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 28}, "spans": [{"start": 9, "end": 17, "label": "EVENT"}, {"start": 29, "end": 39, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7794160842895508}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2014/01/21", "metadata": {"source": "The Light of Truth", "filename": "822.txt", "date": "2014/01/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9236261248588562}
{"text": "SOURCE: News Online Today", "metadata": {"source": "News Online Today", "filename": "544.txt", "date": "2001/08/31", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 25, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8630812764167786}
{"text": "Our sources in the Department of the Interior say us that the tax of 50% tax in the new exploration of the oil and the gas could render superior to $1 billion in fiscal income per year.", "metadata": {"source": "The Guide", "filename": "47.txt", "date": "1993/03/13", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 19, "end": 45, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7797307968139648}
{"text": "Government spokesman Rufus Drymiau commented, \"These sort of violent actions by members of the Protectors of Kronos are counterproductive.", "metadata": {"source": "Central Bulletin", "filename": "113.txt", "date": "2005/09/25", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 21, "end": 34, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 95, "end": 115, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7484838366508484}
{"text": "TITLE: GAStech Profile", "metadata": {"source": "World Source", "filename": "393.txt", "date": "2013/02/22", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 7, "end": 14, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8956717252731323}
{"text": "Continue reading the main story", "metadata": {"source": "World Source", "filename": "643.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9027530550956726}
{"text": "1520 - a relationship from the airport of Abila indicates that a classified airplane has left with eight people around to 2:30 PM.", "metadata": {"source": "Modern Rubicon", "filename": "772.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [{"start": 42, "end": 47, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9510385394096375}
{"text": "Collecting was brought in the war only by the worsening presence of police force Abila in babbling couples.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "116.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 21}, "spans": [{"start": 81, "end": 86, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7157160043716431}
{"text": "SOURCE: International News", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "767.txt", "date": "2010/06/21", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 26, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8485456109046936}
{"text": "We have fallen at least two dozens in previous month, aforesaid Alicia Bianca, nurse manager of the department have.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "530.txt", "date": "2013/02/08", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 64, "end": 77, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8172277212142944}
{"text": "They become to provide with medical care, recreation, and food.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "580.txt", "date": "2013/02/24", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7712768316268921}
{"text": "Besides to direct the two fault WFA also it demands that ascending clean the contamination, that includes stops levels of the benzene, arsenic of the tolueno and xylene, barium, chromium, lead and selenium.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "442.txt", "date": "1998/11/17", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 32, "end": 35, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7060242295265198}
{"text": "SOURCE: International Times\nTITLE: GAStech", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "150.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 27, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 35, "end": 42, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.862456202507019}
{"text": "The WFA declaration demands the extensive contamination of the underground water, a deficiency of suitable safeguards, the demands of the cleaning that are not made case and any negligence of the government.", "metadata": {"source": "The General Post", "filename": "316.txt", "date": "1998/11/14", "sentence_index": 5}, "spans": [{"start": 4, "end": 7, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8636058568954468}
{"text": "The report released by the death of Karel allotted of coroner of town of Abila in July 2010 to the sudden stop, and seeks it was enclosed soon then.", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "523.txt", "date": "2010/06/21", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 36, "end": 41, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 73, "end": 78, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8680972456932068}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Explainer", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "324.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8995077610015869}
{"text": "In a press release today today, President Kapelou called the POK \"a troop of the criminals, gangsters, and the dissatisfied ones who became a plague with our peaceful way of life.\"", "metadata": {"source": "Worldwise", "filename": "792.txt", "date": "2012/06/22", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 42, "end": 49, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 61, "end": 64, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7582167983055115}
{"text": "SOURCE: International News", "metadata": {"source": "International News", "filename": "821.txt", "date": "1999/07/04", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 26, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8485456109046936}
{"text": "Danisliau said to second group of similar passengers \"to celebrate something.\"", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "324.txt", "date": "2014/01/20", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 0, "end": 9, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8394380807876587}
{"text": "\"You don't know what you're getting when you get it,\" Bianca said.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 12}, "spans": [{"start": 54, "end": 60, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8009802103042603}
{"text": "SOURCE: Modern Rubicon\nTITLE: ON SCENE BLOG", "metadata": {"source": "Modern Rubicon", "filename": "772.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 22, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8962264657020569}
{"text": "The trucks stopped in the middle of the road for any reason.\"", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "778.txt", "date": "2001/09/01", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.705140233039856}
{"text": "\"Centrum developed world class expertise in engineering in very difficult surroundings\"", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "638.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [{"start": 1, "end": 8, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.6992780566215515}
{"text": "TITLE: COLLECTION WHICH IS PLANNED TO SUPPORT OF THE RAISED DUTY OF RESPONSIBILITY OF THE GOVERNMENT", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "207.txt", "date": "2012/04/11", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7793595790863037}
{"text": "SOURCE: Kronos Star\nTITLE: Breaking: Emergency at GAStech Headquarters Building [Updates]\nAUTHOR: Cato Rossini, Marcella Trapani\nPUBLISHED: 20 January 2014", "metadata": {"source": "Kronos Star", "filename": "540.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 19, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 50, "end": 57, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 98, "end": 110, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 112, "end": 128, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8900871872901917}
{"text": "In March, the government allotted to GAStech exclusive lines with the fields of state-owned property of curve of Tiskele, the largest little developed gas layer in Europe.", "metadata": {"source": "Worldwise", "filename": "143.txt", "date": "1993/09/21", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 37, "end": 44, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 113, "end": 120, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 164, "end": 170, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9226222634315491}
{"text": "SOURCE: News Desk", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "60.txt", "date": "1997/04/25", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 17, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8559430837631226}
{"text": "There is an argument, however, which the energy matter differing from other industries be, which energy companies require to work in several manners.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "580.txt", "date": "2013/02/24", "sentence_index": 19}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8632287383079529}
{"text": "TITLE: IN REMEMBRANCE:  THE DEATH OF ELIAN KAREL, A YEAR LATER", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "257.txt", "date": "2010/06/21", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 37, "end": 48, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.754686176776886}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2007/04/11", "metadata": {"source": "Athena Speaks", "filename": "48.txt", "date": "2007/04/11", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9186742901802063}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2007/03/21", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "603.txt", "date": "2007/03/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9204076528549194}
{"text": "Manufacturers frequently change the designer drug's chemical composition and its name to stay one step ahead of authorities, Biance said.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 20}, "spans": [{"start": 125, "end": 131, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9229589700698853}
{"text": "The environment situation is desperate.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "88.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 20}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8402454257011414}
{"text": "Q: What is possible foreign CEOs when they to Kronos expects come?", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "535.txt", "date": "2014/03/26", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 46, "end": 52, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9106521606445312}
{"text": "0926 - The reporter they are standing outside of the centers of GAStech that wait for the leaders of GAStech that they are believed that they appear in the hour.", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "597.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 64, "end": 71, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 101, "end": 108, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9111394882202148}
{"text": "It noted that the truck passed in the intersection when the car had the right of the manner.", "metadata": {"source": "World Journal", "filename": "6.txt", "date": "2007/03/20", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.933817446231842}
{"text": "President Dorel Kapelou II gained the re-election with the greatest margin never in an election of Kronesian.", "metadata": {"source": "Athena Speaks", "filename": "601.txt", "date": "2010/10/04", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 23, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 99, "end": 108, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8019044995307922}
{"text": "Civil servants of the government gave that to a short declaration from people insuring of Abila their security of the largest importance are.", "metadata": {"source": "News Desk", "filename": "190.txt", "date": "2010/06/15", "sentence_index": 6}, "spans": [{"start": 90, "end": 95, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8139413595199585}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 20 January 2014", "metadata": {"source": "Centrum Sentinel", "filename": "486.txt", "date": "2009/06/21", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9242470860481262}
{"text": "SOURCE: International Times\nTITLE: Profile:  Elian Karel", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "24.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 27, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 45, "end": 56, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9462047219276428}
{"text": "\"Kronos was horrified from north to south by the hideous crime committed by the POK,\" Mr. Drymiau said.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "514.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [{"start": 1, "end": 7, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 80, "end": 83, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 90, "end": 97, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8259553909301758}
{"text": "Still, the government cannot outright ban cotton candy because manufacturers can alter the recipe and skirt the law, Bianca said.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 25}, "spans": [{"start": 117, "end": 123, "label": "PERSON"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7126500010490417}
{"text": "The apparent confusion stems from the similarity between his name and that of a Protector of Kronos member.", "metadata": {"source": "The Abila Post", "filename": "50.txt", "date": "2013/11/13", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 80, "end": 89, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 93, "end": 99, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7582533359527588}
{"text": "SOURCE: Tethys News\nTITLE: To break off itself: The emergency to GAStech quarters construction [updates]", "metadata": {"source": "Tethys News", "filename": "253.txt", "date": "2009/03/14", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 19, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 65, "end": 72, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8918663859367371}
{"text": "was destroyed, the local press they found communicated people for were considerably given and aid aid decreased.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "302.txt", "date": "1999/11/16", "sentence_index": 21}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8527097702026367}
{"text": "I request:  Where it is the money that goes.", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "157.txt", "date": "2009/03/13", "sentence_index": 11}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7966493964195251}
{"text": "That was in spite of strong levels of the investment, reaching a year last of registry and maintained east year.", "metadata": {"source": "Everyday News", "filename": "80.txt", "date": "2012/02/22", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.696918249130249}
{"text": "The occupants of the vehicles of government left and joined the argument.", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "778.txt", "date": "2001/09/01", "sentence_index": 16}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7703025341033936}
{"text": "TITLE:  THE WHO BRINGS A WEAPON TO SEATING INSIDE?", "metadata": {"source": "Daily Pegasus", "filename": "700.txt", "date": "2013/06/22", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8061745166778564}
{"text": "Whereas the world disclosed the 16 of December of 2013, the international recent initial offer public of GAStech (IPO) produced net Sten Sanjorge, Jr to $1,96 billion eye-that exploded for their part that perforating controlled of the international company and of exploration of the gas.", "metadata": {"source": "The Explainer", "filename": "679.txt", "date": "2010/06/14", "sentence_index": 9}, "spans": [{"start": 105, "end": 112, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 114, "end": 117, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 132, "end": 136, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 137, "end": 145, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8309881687164307}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2001/09/01", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "778.txt", "date": "2001/09/01", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9150760173797607}
{"text": "20 Jan 2014", "metadata": {"source": "Homeland Illumination", "filename": "484.txt", "date": "1996/03/15", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8899763226509094}
{"text": "LOCATION: ABILA, Kronos", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "135.txt", "date": "2012/04/09", "sentence_index": 3}, "spans": [{"start": 10, "end": 15, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 17, "end": 23, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9006855487823486}
{"text": "The signs under protester requested government change and social equality.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "318.txt", "date": "2012/06/21", "sentence_index": 10}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7718743085861206}
{"text": "Citywide, several deaths have been attributed to \"Cotton Candy\" according to the Kronos National Poison Center.", "metadata": {"source": "International Times", "filename": "651.txt", "date": "2009/02/23", "sentence_index": 7}, "spans": [{"start": 50, "end": 62, "label": "EVENT"}, {"start": 81, "end": 110, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.7543689012527466}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 2009/03/12", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "683.txt", "date": "2009/03/12", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9143324494361877}
{"text": "He looked at and sounded this way good.", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "445.txt", "date": "2009/06/20", "sentence_index": 13}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9222446084022522}
{"text": "Whereas the overall press which is communicated more than 2500 people was killed and 100,000 bldg.", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "302.txt", "date": "1999/11/16", "sentence_index": 20}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8770269751548767}
{"text": "PUBLISHED: 1999/11/15", "metadata": {"source": "News Online Today", "filename": "117.txt", "date": "1999/11/15", "sentence_index": 2}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.9227825999259949}
{"text": "really high is", "metadata": {"source": "The Continent", "filename": "268.txt", "date": "2009/06/23", "sentence_index": 15}, "spans": [], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.6983782052993774}
{"text": "At the request of the citizens of Elodis, Wellness for All has published a report on the impact of gas drilling operations on water quality and public health.", "metadata": {"source": "All News Today", "filename": "617.txt", "date": "1998/05/16", "sentence_index": 4}, "spans": [{"start": 34, "end": 40, "label": "ORG"}, {"start": 42, "end": 58, "label": "ORG"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8908675909042358}
{"text": "TITLE: MINISTER OF HEALTH TO PROPOSE SOLUTION TO THE POISONING OF THE CITY", "metadata": {"source": "The Wrap", "filename": "740.txt", "date": "1999/07/09", "sentence_index": 1}, "spans": [{"start": 7, "end": 15, "label": "PERSON"}, {"start": 70, "end": 74, "label": "LOC"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8905479311943054}
{"text": "SOURCE: The Orb", "metadata": {"source": "The Orb", "filename": "239.txt", "date": "2012/04/10", "sentence_index": 0}, "spans": [{"start": 8, "end": 11, "label": "LOC"}, {"start": 12, "end": 15, "label": "EVENT"}], "stance": "STANCE_NEU", "score": 0.8945004343986511}
